WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
What are you doing?
I feel like you don't believe me.
It's starting to drive me crazy.
It's not fair that you don't believe me.
When have I ever lied to you?
I believe you.
Obviously, you don't. Or you
wouldn't be acting like this.
And it's...
It's fucked up. We've always
been honest with each other.
So, just... give me a break.
- No, we haven't.
- We haven't?
I mean, we're not honest about...
About what?
About how we're not
attracted to each other...
anymore.
Or at least you're not
attracted to me, you know?
It's, like, I get it you're
on top of the world right now.
You could sleep with...
... whoever you want,
- and you're stuck with me and...
- Stop saying that stuff!
Yeah, it makes sense that
you'd wanna have sex
with an Italian hooker.
- You're not getting any.
- I didn't have sex
with an Italian hooker. Jesus, fuck!
I'm just saying that
it's not the cheating
- that bothers me so much...
- There was no cheating!
There was no cheating!
... as what it says about us.
What?
What does it say?
That maybe something has died.
We are too young to be this old, Ethan.
I'm sure you don't want that
part of your life to be over.
Do you?
I don't.
I'm dealing with a lot, okay?
Work's been insane. And...
Okay.
I don't know. I... I...
We can work on it.
We can work on it, okay?
Do even want me?
I love you.
- So depressing.
- "I love you" is depressing?
No. No.
I love you, too.
Are you gonna go running or what?
I don't know.
- You want a coffee?
- Yes, please.
You know, she's pretty convinced
you guys did something bad
- when we were in Noto.
- Ooh, something bad?
- Mm.
- Like what?
I don't know.
- What'd you do this time?
- I told you. We partied.
- How hard did you party?
- So hard, honey.
- Yeah?
- So...
fucking hard!
- Because you left me.
- Oh.
- Yeah. You abandoned me.
- Yeah?
And now, you must pay.
What about you?
You fuck anyone in Noto?
Any fat Italian guys
with BO and a dirty dick?
- Every single one.
- You little...
Oh, yeah.
- Oh, you're gonna pay.
- Mm.
- So, how was the opera?
- She died.
- Who?
- Madame Butterfly.
- Oh.
How was your big night?
It was fun.
Yeah. We almost got arrested.
We didn't pay for our arancini. So,
- yeah.
- Arancinis cost a dollar.
I know.
Maybe you should slow
down with this guy.
Why?
Something about his
relationship with his uncle.
What about it?
- I don't think it's his uncle.
- It is.
- Mm-mm.
- Why would you say that?
Oh, it was just a...
It was just a strong hunch.
Okay?
Portia.
When I see you, I... I see
a younger version of me.
You know, when I was a little girl,
my mother used to dress
me up like a little doll.
And I was always a little doll,
waiting for someone to play with me.
You know, when you're empty inside
and you have no direction,
you'll end up in some
crazy places, right?
But you'll still be lost.
What are you trying to say? Like...
Get your shit together, Portia.
Buongiorno, ladies.
Pineapple mimosa?
- Mm. Yes.
- Oh, sure.
- How did we sleep?
- Not great.
There were some strange
noises in the night.
Oh, no.
Well, we need you refreshed,
you're guest of honor tonight.
Oh.
Today's the big day!
Gonna visit the motherland.
Wouldn't it be cool
if we actually found
some blood relations?
You know, uh, Marty Fiorina,
he did something like
this, but in Puglia.
Found his entire extended family.
They had a big lunch,
they drank wine, they took photos.
Oh. A real homecoming.
- That would be nice.
- I found us a translator.
Good thinking.
Sì.
Buongiorno!
Buongiorno.
Salvatore? Salvatore!
Hey!
- What are you trying to do?
- What do you mean?
Are you trying not to pay us?
- Were you not paid?
- You owe us 1,300 Euros.
I'll get it sorted, we have money.
I... I didn't realize you
hadn't been paid, okay?
Yes.
- Ciao.
Salvatore?
Grazie.
- Ah, sì?
- Sì
Grazie!
Hey.
What?
I just saw you talking to those hookers.
I'm so hungover.
I think the only thing I can
do today is lay on the beach.
Detox.
- Please stop gaslighting me.
- I'm not gaslighting you.
Look, I can explain,
just can we please not
talk about it right now?
Okay, whatever.
I'm over it. I don't...
I don't care anymore.
Just looking at all those
sausages made me wanna puke.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
- Sorry.
- Shit!
Scared the widdle baby, did I?
Right.
I got the car for the day.
Do you wanna take a drive?
We'll go down to Cefalù,
we'll drink some Peronis,
eat some ice cream. What do you think?
- Sure, yeah!
- Yeah?
I'm down for anything.
I just wanna be back for
the party thing later.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- We'll be back. Don't worry.
- Okay.
Uh, go grab all your shit,
meet me by the car, all right?
Got me uncle's credit card, so,
you know.
- All right. Go.
- Oh, fuck!
- Oh my God!
- Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry,
- I was just teasing.
- So mean!
Shit!
Is that...
Wouldn't it be incredible
if we actually found
some distant relatives?
Would be amazing.
Just try not to fall before
we get you in the car, Dad.
- Oh. Thanks a lot, Dom!
- Hey, guys.
This is Lucia. She's
going to translate for us.
This is my dad, Dominic,
and my grandfather, Bert.
My pleasure. Good morning!
- Hi.
- I've seen you around.
- Ah, yes! I am always around.
- I love this hotel, so...
- Hey, Lucia?
Oh! Just... just one second.
Sorry, Albie, I thought you meant, um,
someone who worked here in the hotel.
Is there a problem?
Oh, I... I don't know
if this is a good idea.
Dad, she's coming, okay? So, be polite.
You're overreacting.
- Giving yourself away.
- What? Giving what away?
That you slept with her.
Stop it, please. I
don't want her to come.
What's wrong with you?
Can't you just be cool?
Get it together.
Okay, guys. What... Uh,
let's... let's do this.
You seem to know a
lot of the staff here.
Uh. Yes. Uh, he is the
brother of a friend of mine.
- Ah!
- Thank you.
So, tell us about yourself,
my dear. Where are you from?
I'm from Catania.
Ah. How do you speak such good English?
From school. And... from my work.
Oh, what do you?
Hospitality.
High unemployment rate in
Sicily, I hear, so it's...
it's great that you're employed!
Thank you, yes. I'm lucky.
I really wanna get a
massage before we go home.
Do you wanna get massages today?
Yeah, sure.
'Kay, I'm gonna call and see
if they have any availability.
Want me to get you another towel?
Dude!
Can we sit here?
- You are fucking me up here!
- What? How?
Harper is, like, 100 percent
convinced I cheated on her.
- But you didn't, man.
- I know that!
But, could you at least, like, I dunno,
vouch for me or something?
Hi! I was wondering,
do you have room for
two for a massage today?
Oh. Okay.
Yeah. Daphne Sullivan.
109.
Thanks.
Okay.
I got the last massage,
but it's, like, right now.
- Are you sure you don't want it?
- No, you take it.
You're the one going home
to a house full of kids.
Um. Okay, I'm gonna go,
'cause I wanna use the steam room.
Yeah. Yeah, totally.
So... but I'll see you in a few hours?
- Take your time.
- Bye.
E, you wanna go get some drinks, man?
No, I'm good.
- I'll go.
- Yeah?
Yeah. Let's do it.
Hmm.
Do you have any goals?
What?
- Goals?
- Yeah.
- What are some of your goals?
- I don't know.
Be satisfied?
Yeah, that'd be nice.
I think you just gotta
live every day as it comes,
do you know what I mean?
Like, that's what I'd do anyway.
Who knows if we're even
gonna be here tomorrow?
Yeah.
That's very true. The
world's a fucked-up place.
So...
What's wrong with it?
Are you joking?
Pretty fucking good world, I'd say.
Literally everything's falling apart.
You'd rather live in the
Middle Ages then, would ya?
When they were ripping
each other to shreds, yeah?
They were way worse than
ISIS or any of them lot.
Like, it's a fucking miracle
anyone's even left in Europe.
All we've been doing is just
fuckin' hacking each other to bits
and burning each other at the stake.
I'm ready for another beer.
All I'm saying is, right,
we're fucking lucky,
do you know what I mean?
Like, we're living in the...
best time in the history of the world,
on the best fucking planet.
If you can't be satisfied
living now, here...
you're never gonna be satisfied.
So, let's get pissed, eh?
- Come on.
- My...
- I'll grab that.
- Wait! Wait!
Not much to it.
- Hmm.
- No wonder they all left.
Who would I have been if I lived here?
You wouldn't have lived
here, you would've left.
There are people who stay and
there are people who leave.
- And I'm someone who leaves?
- Hmm,
'cause you got wanderlust.
You get that from me.
All righty.
Okay. All right, um, you're
not gonna believe this.
We just talked to
that woman and she said
that there is a Di Grasso
family still living here
and she knows them.
- You're kidding!
- Amazing!
They live a mile down the road,
and she gave us the address.
- Let's go!
- Oh!
- What's wrong?
- Alessio.
- He followed us here?
- Albie, come on.
Could you please drive?
- Please?
- Something wrong?
Dad, start the car. Let's go.
What?
Can you tell me what's going on, please?
- There's some guys following us.
- Who?
Just some guys Lucia knows.
What should I do?
Just pull over. Stop!
I'll talk to him.
What should we do? What do we do here?
Dad, I don't know.
- Hey.
- What's going on here?
No.
I'm going with him.
No, we're not gonna let that
happen. We can handle him.
No, you can't.
Do you want us to call the police?
The police? No! No, no, no, no.
Listen, guys. I'm fine.
He's upset, I just
have to talk with him.
We can't let you go with him. No.
Yeah, but we're also not
gonna escalate things further.
Please! Don't let this spoil your day.
Have your reunion and...
see you tonight. Okay? I'm fine.
- You're sure?
- Yes.
Okay.
- All right.
- I will call you.
- Okay.
- I'm fine.
What happened?
You're gonna just let her get abducted?
That's what she wanted, Dad.
Oh, no.
Don't go with him!
No, that was yesterday!
Hello?
- Hold on, just one second.
- Hello?
What the fuck?
Jesus!
So impatient!
Why did you latch the door?
I didn't know I did.
What? You obviously did.
Habit, I guess?
Since when is latching
the door your habit?
I had a tequila shot at the
bar, I wasn't really thinking.
You had a tequila shot, and then
you had to come up to get a hat?
Yeah, I felt like I was getting burned.
Let's go back down.
Why is this door open?
Is it? I don't know.
- I have no idea.
- Was Cameron in here?
- No.
- Where is he?
Uh. Pr... probably in his room.
He said had to get something, too. Why?
So, you came up here together?
Yeah? So? What is your deal?
- This door should be locked.
- Then lock it.
Hey, guys. Wait up.
Came to get my book. Come on.
Are you coming?
Now what?
We came all this way.
Might as well go in.
Yeah.
Hello, uh, we don't, uh, speak...
Non parlo Italiano. But, uh, my name...
is Dominic Di Grasso.
Di Grasso.
You are Di Grasso, sì?
Sì.
My mother was from Testa dell'Acqua.
From here.
She left to go to America.
Sì. Now, uh, we've come back
to find where we're from.
Um, we think that, uh, we are related.
You're our relatives.
You and I are cousins!
Cousins.
Um...
- Cugini!
- Cugini.
Huh?
Could we say buongiorno,
uh, a tua madre?
Eh.
Woah.
Grazie.
Signora.
We are your cousins from America.
My mother was from Testa dell'Acqua!
From here!
Huh?
No, no.
No, no, no, no. We come in peace!
I think we should leave.
- No, we're related. We're rel...
- Come on. Dad, Nonno, let's go.
Nonno, we should go. Let's go.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Sorry, guys.
Bah!
Let's get outta here.
Not quite what I imagined.
He is a slimeball.
I didn't mean to say he's,
like, my best friend or anything.
I just want you to admit it, that's all.
Yeah. I'd... he can be
a fun time. That's all.
That's all I meant.
You wanna try this?
It's actually kinda good.
Why are you in a good mood?
What?
Now, all of a sudden,
you're in a good mood? Why?
Because we're in Sicily,
and it's beautiful!
And because...
at the bar, Cameron confirmed
everything that you said.
- He did?
- Yeah. Basically.
Hi!
- What's up, honey?
- Okay, guys.
- Don't hate me, but, wow!
- What?
- That massage was amazing!
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's awesome.
- I'm happy for you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Well,
then you'll also be happy
to know that my masseur
- was so hot.
- What?
- Yeah.
- No!
Kinda looked like Timothée Chalamet.
- Oh, nice!
- But he had muscles.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
Timothée Sham-a-lay?
Tell me he didn't touch your boobs.
- I asked him to.
- Dirty slut!
- Are you jealous?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- I want a fucking divorce!
- Cam! Stop it!
- Oh! You are...
- Just kidding.
- Mm.
Whoo! Fucking hell!
I fucking love beer,
- know what I mean?
- Yeah, I know.
How's your thing?
- It's good, yeah.
- Yeah?
Uh, do you feel like we should
head back to the house soon?
I feel like the party's
probably starting. I mean...
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck that, fuck that.
Uh, let's get another one.
Geezer?
Can we get, uh, two more, yeah?
Nice one.
Nah, don't worry.
My uncle's parties, they start
late and they finish late.
So, we're good.
Fuck me sideways.
Oh, my God.
You look stunning.
No, stunning.
- Turn around.
- No.
- Come on.
- No, my ass looks big.
No, it d... Come on.
Let's see your big, beautiful arse
in that amazing symphony of salmon.
Yes!
- And there's more good news.
- Yeah?
I found the perfect arm
candy for you tonight.
What do you mean?
I mean literally the sexiest
heterosexual in Palermo.
- Oh. Who is this person?
- Niccolò. Gorgeous.
Notoriously well-hung. Not that
I've seen it firsthand...
... he said, crestfallen.
But believe me, I've tried.
Well, what does he do for a living?
Oh, this and that.
Niccolò may or may not have ties
to a very influential local family.
Oh, he joined the mafia?
Did I say that? I didn't say that.
We don't use that word in Palermo.
I know Niccolò because
he supplies all my parties
with the best party favors.
Yeah, but, I'm not gonna be his type.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's in the bag, as they say.
Come on. There are people here.
Here's Penelope Bianchi.
- Nice to meet you.
My dear friend, Emily
Fitzroy. Peppe Tasca.
What an honor.
They're lovely people, but
we could be there all night.
Okay.
Oh, Niccolò. Here he is.
Hello. Hey.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Piacere.
- Mm.
Yeah. Are you S... Sicilian?
- Yes. I'm from Palermo.
- Oh.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Little pick-me-up?
I'm, uh... I haven't
done that in a long time.
It's like riding a bike.
Oh.
Oh. Oh.
- Let's do it.
- Uh. Okay.
- Okay.
- Here.
- Do you feel it?
- I do.
- Yeah.
- It's very pure.
Yeah. And fresh, yeah.
Well, this is going
rather well, isn't it?
I... I love your giant pupils.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We will have fun tonight.
- Ciao.
Ah! Uh, sì. Sì. Uh...
Okay.
Ah! Sì.
No, no, no.
Grazie.
Okay.
Ah.
Grazie.
- Um...
- Uh...
Okay. Okay. Grazie.
Grazie.
I don't know why they
keep giving us these menus.
We know 'em back to front by now.
You... you okay, man?
Harper told me that you,
uh, said something to her.
Yeah.
Of course. I said, uh, you know,
you had done nothing wrong
and you've been a good boy.
Stop flirting with my
wife. I'm not a fool.
All right.
D... Dude, are you being serious?
Were you in our room?
- What? When?
- Today.
Were you? In our room?
No. Of course not.
I know you got naked in front of her.
- What?
- On the first day...
What... what are you talking about?
... when you borrowed my bathing suit.
I know what you're doing, man.
E, are you... losing it?
Were you in our fucking room, man?
Just tell me the tru...
Oh, well, you have to get a studio.
Can't be consistent with
the classes, you know?
Yeah. I struggle with that, too.
Oh, my gosh, wow.
I actually think little Timmy Chalamet
did fuck up my back.
- It's starting to really hurt.
- Oh, sorry.
No.
- Do you have any aspirin?
- Uh. I think I might.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
♪ Watch the sun rise ♪
♪ On a tropic isle ♪
♪ Just remember, darling ♪
♪ All the while ♪
♪ You belong to me ♪
♪ See the marketplace in old Algiers ♪
Grazie.
♪ Send me photographs and souvenirs ♪
♪ Just remember when a dream appears ♪
Dad?
♪ You belong to me ♪
You okay?
You always think there's
gonna be a homecoming.
The embrace of a woman...
who tells you you've done all right.
Well, there is no homecoming.
Not for me, not anymore.
Not very hungry.
Think I'ma just get a drink
at the lounge.
♪ Fly the ocean in a silver plane ♪
♪ See the jungle when
it's wet with rain ♪
♪ Just remember ♪
♪ When I'm home again ♪
♪ You belong to ♪
♪ Me ♪
Grazie.
You know, you're really very good.
Well, you're better than the last guy.
- Oh.
- He was... terrible.
Grazie.
Well, I have one fan.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
I love Palermo.
Palermo loves you.
- Ah!
- I'm... Wait.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
- About this room.
- No.
- Nobody knows.
- This is our secret place.
- Wow.
- Oh, wait a minute.
Can we look in your cocaine bag?
- Yeah, sure.
- 'Cause I...
- I want some more.
- Yeah.
Ooh, look.
- You got a gun.
- Wow! You...
- And I always carry it with me.
You got a... What were
you doing with a gun?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
- That is so sexy.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I want it.
- You wanna start?
Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh.
Huh.
No.
Okay.
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Okay.
What does he want from you?
He wants to control me.
He won't let me go, you know.
What would it take
for him to let you go?
Money. He says I owe him.
I make a lot of money for
him. I told you, he is crazy.
But it's not your problem.
Why we going? It's too early.
No, it's... it's time to go.
♪ I'm forever blowing bubbles ♪
♪ Pretty bubbles ♪
Oi!
Watch where you're
fucking going, you cunt!
Sorry. Sorry.
- Hey, hey. Hey.
- What's wrong with ya?
Dickhead!
Sorry.
- Hey. Look, look. Let's just... Let's...
- Vaffanculo... you fuckin' prick.
You wanna go to the party?
- Let's go to the party. Yeah?
- What? Oh.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, we can't drive. We're too drunk.
It's all right. We'll
just get a hotel, yeah?
I got my uncle's credit card. Yeah?
Why is it so sad? Smile.
Ah, it's just a bunch of
fuckin' gays and old hags.
We'll make our own party,
yeah? And we'll be satisfied.
Finally be satisfied. Mwah!
♪ Fortune's always hiding ♪
♪ I've looked everywhere ♪
♪ I'm forever blowing bubbles ♪
♪ Pretty bubbles in the air! ♪
United!
Hello?
- Hold on, just one second.
- Hello?
Jesus! So impatient.
I found my Ambien. Do you want one?
- Huh?
- Do you want an Ambien?
Uh. No.
- Oh.
- Away from the public, okay?
Yeah?
Oh. I don't speak Italian.
Thought I told you.
- Okay. I come back.
- Mm. Okay.
- Just give me one second.
- Mm. Mm.
Oh. Oh. Oh.
Wow.
Oh.
Wow!
Uh. I'm... I'm so nervous.
Just sit down.
Mm.
It's just...
You're just really handsome.
- Yeah?
- I don't know...
Mm.
Hey.
Oh, it's a nice room, innit?
Yeah. It's fine, I guess.
Well, it's free.
Must be nice to have a rich uncle.
Yeah, well...
... he's not rich.
Not really anyway. He's
spent most of it, hasn't he?
You've seen the way he lives.
Got his boat.
His house.
These fucking princesses, and lords,
and these posh fuckers, yeah?
They got their palazzos.
They ain't got no money.
He was gonna have to sell Villa Pisano.
It's his family's fucking house!
Your family, too, though, right?
Because he's your uncle. Right?
That would have fucking killed him.
But he doesn't have to?
Well, he's coming into
money now, isn't he?
Is he?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
And he's gonna help his friends.
'Cause he's... he's... he's very giving.
I'm just happy that...
that I get to, you know,
help him now.
'Cause he's helped me.
How are you helping him?
I was in a fucking hole.
You know, you complain
about your life, yeah?
But really, you should just shut it,
'cause you ain't never been
in a fuckin' hole like that.
Nah.
And then he comes along and...
You know, no one's perfect.
Sometimes you do things
you don't wanna do.
- You know?
- No...
What do you mean? What kind of hole?
Fucking deep hole, man.
Very fucking deep.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -